Hello, everyone.
Hello.
I'm Minami Umezawa.
I'm Sakura Endo.
I'm Matsumier.
I'm Mao Iwaki.
These four of us are here in Osaka today.
Yay!
Osaka!
Are we in Osaka?
Of course we are in Osaka!
Doesn't it look like Osaka?
It sure does.
Wow!
Nogizaka is now streaming!
In commemoration of our one millionth channel subscriber!
We're going to make your dreams come true in the second installment of this project.
Who is the dreamer who came to help us this time out of the 12,000 or so submissions we received?
Manami, 19 years old!
I am a second-year student at Osaka Bunka Fashion College Super Designer Department.
I created a piece of work when I was a freshman, but I didn't have a chance to actually have the opportunity to visit the school.
It makes me very sad to think that everyone's wonderful works will be put away in the back of my house.
That's when I came across this project, and I thought that if everyone could wear them, it would be a great opportunity to show them off.
I thought that if everyone could wear them, their beautiful costumes would shine even more brightly, so I decided to apply.
I hope you will consider it.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy, Manami!
Does that mean we will be allowed to wear the clothes?
Yes, that's right.
I'm a little nervous about being 19, huh?
I'm you.
Wow.
Wow. Okay.
You wanna go? Okay, bye.
You want to go? Okay, bye.
Let's go.
Let's go!
So the four of us headed to Osaka City's clothing school
Osaka Bunka Fashion College.
Excuse me.
We went to the classroom where Manami-san, who applied for the job, was waiting for us.
It might not be Manami-san.
Here you go, Mo-chan!
Yes, Mo-chan.
Mo-chan's having fun.
Having fun, having fun.
Let's go.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Hello. - Hello.
Are you sure it's Manami-san?
Yes, I am.
Nice to meet you.
This is Manami Makifuji, a second-year student at Osaka Bunka Fashion College.
I'm very nervous.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, it's like it's four against one.
Have you always been a fan of Nogizaka?
Yes, since I was in junior high school.
I went to an event at Nishinomiya Gardens just around the time Sakura Endo joined the group.
I went to an event at Nishinomiya Gardens.
Is that right?
Is that new?
Yes, that's it.
I remember.
I remember it.
I'm so glad.
Hey, that's great.
Thank you very much.
Manami-san, the reason why you applied for this project is...
We've all made three outfits in a year.
But we didn't have much of a chance to show them off.
We didn't have a chance to show them off.
But we all worked so hard on them.
I was wondering if there was a chance to do so.
I came across the application for this project.
I thought it would be great if Ms. Nogizaka could wear it.
so I decided to apply.
What was the theme of the project?
I was inspired by leaves.
inspired by leaves.
Did you do all the sewing yourself?
Yes, I did.
From the design
From the design.
That's amazing.
Do designs just come to you out of the blue?
The teacher worked really hard to come up with a lot of ideas.The teacher worked really hard to come up with a lot of ideas.
I consulted with the teachers and others to make it.
In the Super Designer Department, where Manami goes to school
costume making started in the first grade.
She didn't know what was right and what was left.
with her teachers and friends.
the work was created from scratch.
Although an exhibition was held in March, she had no chance to actually have people wear them.
but there was no opportunity to have people actually wear them.
I had a dream to have not only myself but also
She has a dream to have everyone's work worn by others.
Does everyone in the class know about this project?
I haven't told them at all.
That's scary.
I hope they know.
I see.
They just said they'd be covering the event from Tokyo.
They didn't say who was coming.
I see.
That's the best way to put it.
That's the scariest part.
It's possible they've raised the bar.
Do they know... about us?
Maybe.
Maybe you know us.
I'm scared.
It's my own insecurity.
Do the kids around you know that Ms. Nogami likes Nogizaka?
I'm still a little nervous about the surprise appearance of the four of us.
But I'm sure the Super Designers Department will be happy to have them.
As originally planned, the interview was to be conducted from Tokyo.
We gathered in the classroom without knowing who was coming.
I wonder if Manami's dream will please everyone in the class.
Good afternoon.
Excuse me.
Is it okay if I leave?
Yes, you may come in.
I'm sorry to barge in.
My name is Wheat 46.
Congratulations!
Today, we have our own YouTube channel.
We're looking for projects to make our fans' dreams come true.
Manami-san applied for it.
That's right.
We are here today to make that dream come true!
What do you study in this department?
Is it mainly design?
Design?
Well, yes, of course.
Do you have any dreams for the future?
A fashion designer.
That's cool.
Pink.
Do you have a point of reference for your clothes?
I like pink.
I wear pink basically.
I prefer vivid colors to light colors.
Do you go to school in plain clothes every day?
Yes, I do.
It must be tough.
I guess it's not that hard.
Surprisingly, we all wear T-shirts and pants.
It's okay.
The surprise appearance was a success.
Do you have a favorite brand?
I wonder if I can use it.
Now that you've got a feel for the class...
I was wondering if I could wear some of the pieces you made in your first year.
I'd like to wear it today.
Is that okay?
Please wear it.
I'd love to.
The four of you leave the room to change into your costumes.
This time, we will use this classroom to wear our costumes in a fashion show style.
My dream is to have my own brand in the future.
I hope to become a designer who can be active in the world.
Do you want to work abroad?
We are the same age.
To support students of my generation who are pursuing their dreams
And to make Manami's dream come true.
The one-day fashion show is about to start!
Cute!
So cute!
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10
Thank you very much.
Ooh!
Inaudible Music
GEDHOFF teddy
It's a basic double-ring opening.
These will be pulled on the same day.
Thank you very much for your time.
Oh!Ooh!
Ooh!
Oshiroi!
Thank you for your hard work.
congratulations!
Woooo!
Yay!
[Applause]
Thank you very much for your hard work.
One, two, three.
Thank you very much for your hard work!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Very nice!
Wow, so beautiful!
beautiful
wow!
cool!
outro
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work
applause
Music
music
Smash
Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Amazing!
This is amazing.
So, we got to try on the costumes that you all designed and created, how did you like them?
I've never had anyone wear it before, and I was wondering how it would look like if a model actually wore it.
It's totally different from what it looks like when you try it on and have a real cute person put it on you.
I'm so happy and really moved by having a real cute person wear it.
Thank you so much for giving me this opportunity to wear the blouse with my aunt.
I'm sorry the flower fell off.
I'm sorry I should have made it sturdier.
Thank you anyway.
When I saw you wearing it, I was so surprised that it wasn't yours. I'm going to work on it.
I couldn't imagine it really working.
I couldn't imagine it moving, so thank you so much!
It's so amazing that I can't believe it was made by a student.
It was so much fun and I was so moved to wear such a delicate costume that you spent so much time on.
It was so much fun and I was so moved.
It was a very happy time for me.
Thank you so much!
Thank you so much for letting me wear such beautiful costumes.
I was so happy to be able to wear such beautiful costumes and to have such a wonderful live performance.
I was so happy and moved.
I was very moved.
Thank you so much!
I've never been a model before.
It was one of my dreams to be able to do it someday.
I had a lot of fun wearing the clothes that everyone in my age group made for me.
It was a lot of fun to be able to wear something made by people my own age.
I was so happy to be able to wear the clothes that everyone in my age group made for me.
I was so happy to be able to wear the clothes that were made with so much effort.
Thank you very much for this precious experience!
So, Manami, were we able to help you with your dream?
Were you able to? I'm so glad!
I was very happy too, and I was glad that everyone in the class was happy, which made me think that it was a good idea to apply for the contest.
Thank you so much!
I am so moved that I am at a loss for words, but for now, I am a big fan from today!
Next!
Second place!
Thank you very much.